<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kdegraphics_thumbnailers</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.gwenview.desktop</extends>
  <name>kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">kdegraphics-koadro-txiki-egileak</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE-grafik miniatyrbilder</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxkdegraphics-thumbnailersxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">kdegraphics-thumbnailers</name>
  <summary>Graphics file format thumbnailers for KDE applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Miniatures per als formats de fitxer de gràfics per a les aplicacions KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Vorschaubilder von grafischen Dateiformaten für KDE-Anwendungen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Εικόνες επισκόπησης tvn τύπων αποθήκευσης αρχείων γραφικών για τις εφαρmογές του KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Graphics file format thumbnailers for KDE applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Generadores de miniaturas de formatos gráficos para aplicaciones de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Graafikafaili vormingus pisipildid KDE rakendustele</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">KDE aplikazioetarako formatu grafikoen koadro-txiki egilea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Luo grafiikkatiedostoista pienoiskuvat KDE-sovelluksiin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Créateurs de vignettes de fichiers au format graphique pour les applications KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Generatori di miniature dei file di formati grafici per le applicazioni di KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KDE 프로그램의 그래픽 파일 미리 보기 도구</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Grafisch bestandsformaat van miniaturen voor KDE toepassingen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Miniatyrbiletlagar for ymse grafikkformat for bruk i KDE-program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Twórcy miniatur dla plików graficznych dla aplikacji KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Miniaturas de formatos de ficheiros gráficos para as aplicações do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Miniaturas de formatos de arquivo gráficos para os aplicativos do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Создание миниатюр графических файлов для приложений KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Miniatúry formátov grafických súborov pre aplikácie KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Miniatyrbilder för grafikfilformat för KDE-program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Засоби створення мініатюр вмісту файлів із графікою для програм KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxGraphics file format thumbnailers for KDE applicationsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE 应用程序的图形文件缩略图产生器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">適用於 KDE 應用程式的圖形檔案格式縮圖產生工具</summary>
  <description>
    <p>These plugins allow KDE software to create thumbnails for advanced graphic file formats PostScript and Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquests connectors permeten que el programari KDE creï miniatures per als formats de fitxer de gràfics avançats PostScript i RAW.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit diesem Modul können KDE-Anwendungen Vorschaubilder für die Grafikformate PostScript und Raw erstellen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αυτά τα πρόσθετα επιτρέπουν στο λογισμικό του KDE να δημιουργεί εικόνες επισκόπησης για προηγμένους τύπους αποθήκευσης αρχείων PostScript και Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">These plugins allow KDE software to create thumbnails for advanced graphic file formats PostScript and Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Estos complementos permiten a las aplicaciones de KDE crear miniaturas de los formatos de archivos gráficos avanzados PostScript y Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Need pluginad lubavad KDE tarkvaral luua pisipilte täiustatud graafikafailide vormingutele PostScript ja Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Plugin honek KDE softwareari PostScript eta Raw formatu grafiko aurreratuen koadro-txikiak sortzen laguntzen dio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Näillä liitännäisillä KDE-sovellukset luovat pienoiskuvia edistyneistä kuvatiedostomuodoista (PostScript ja Raw).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ces modules externes permettent aux logiciels KDE de créer des vignettes pour les formats de fichiers graphiques avancés PostScript et Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Queste estensioni permettono al software di KDE di creare le miniature dei formati di file grafici avanzati PostScript e Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 플러그인을 사용하여 KDE 프로그램에서 포스트스크립트나 RAW와 같은 복잡한 그래픽 파일 형식의 미리 보기 그림을 만들 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Deze plug-ins bieden KDE software om miniaturen aan te maken voor geavanceerde grafische bestandsformaten PostScript en Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Desse programtillegga gjer det mogleg for KDE-programvare å laga miniatyrbilete for avanserte grafikkformat, for eksempel PostScript og råbilete.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Te wtyczki umożliwiają oprogramowaniu KDE tworzenie miniatur dla zaawansowanych formatów graficznych PostScript oraz Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Estes 'plugins' permitem às aplicações do KDE criarem miniaturas de formatos de ficheiros gráficos avançados, como o PostScript e o RAW.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Estes plugins permitem aos aplicativos do KDE criarem miniaturas de formatos de arquivo gráficos avançados, como PostScript e RAW.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Эти подключаемые модули служат для создания миниатюр файлов форматов PostScript и RAW в приложениях KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Tieto doplnky umožňujú softvéru KDE vytvárať miniatúry pre pokročilé formáty grafických súborov PostScript a Raw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Insticksprogrammen låter KDE-programvara skapa miniatyrbilder för de avancerade grafikformaten Postscript och obehandlade filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ці додатки уможливлюють створення мініатюр вмісту для файлів графічних даних, зокрема PostScript та цифрових негативів (RAW), у програмах KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThese plugins allow KDE software to create thumbnails for advanced graphic file formats PostScript and Raw.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">这些插件允许 KDE 软件创建高级图形文件格式 PostScript 和 Raw 的缩略图。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">這些外掛程式讓 KDE 應用程式能建立進階圖形檔案格式 (PostScript 及 Raw) 的縮圖。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdegraphics-thumbnailers/kdegraphics-thumbnailers.png</image>
      <caption>Dolphin with PostScript thumbnail</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Dolphin amb miniatures PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Dolphin mit der Vorschau einer PostScript-Datei</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Το Dolphin με εικόνα επισκόπησης PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Dolphin with PostScript thumbnail</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Dolphin con miniaturas de PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Dolphin PostScripti pisipildiga</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Dolphin PostScript baten koadro-txiki batekin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">PostScript-pienoiskuva Dolphinissa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Dolphin avec une vignette PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Dolphin con le miniature PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">포스트스크립트 미리 보기가 표시된 Dolphin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Dolphin met PostScript-miniatuur</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Dolphin med miniatyrbilete for PostScript-fil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Dolphin z miniaturami PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">O Dolphin com uma miniatura de PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">O Dolphin com miniatura de PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Миниатюра файла в формате PostScript в диспетчере файлов Dolphin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Dolphin s miniatúrou PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Dolphin med miniatyrbild för Postscript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Dolphin із мініатюрою файла PostScript</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxDolphin with PostScript thumbnailxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">使 Dolphin 支持 PostScript 缩略图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">Dolphin 和 PostScript 縮圖</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">application-postscript</icon>
</component>
